{
    "subject": "resource/Viktor_Bolkhovitinov",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Viktor Bolkhovitinov is Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.966164231300354,
            "question": "What is Viktor Bolkhovitinov's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.95773845911026,
            "question": "What is the meaning of 'Fedorovich' in Viktor Bolkhovitinov's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9445643424987793,
            "question": "Which name part of Viktor Bolkhovitinov's full name identifies him specifically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9393097162246704,
            "question": "What are the two given names of Viktor Bolkhovitinov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9186974167823792,
            "question": "What is the middle name of Viktor Bolkhovitinov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182581901550293,
            "question": "What is the last name of Viktor Bolkhovitinov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902378678321838,
            "question": "Does Viktor Bolkhovitinov have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773879408836365,
            "question": "How many parts are there to Viktor Bolkhovitinov's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.840002715587616,
            "question": "Which part of Viktor Bolkhovitinov's name comes first?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5875481963157654,
            "question": "If you were to greet Viktor Bolkhovitinov formally, what would you say?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Viktor Bolkhovitinov is Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1154_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which part of Viktor Bolkhovitinov's name comes first?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1154_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many parts are there to Viktor Bolkhovitinov's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1154_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Viktor Bolkhovitinov have a middle name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1154_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1154_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov, and it confirms that his full name is indeed Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Viktor Fedorovich Bolkhovitinov, confirming his full name as stated in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}